Finding Aid for Museum of Art (University of Michigan) records, 1946-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibition Files, 1946-2003
  - 1963-1964
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1963-1964
      - "Mrs. Forsyth-Classical Art,", October 17, 1963-January 8, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Leon Dabo (1868-1960): A Retrospective Exhibition,", November 13-December 8, 1963 (Box 5)
        (includes correspondence with the artist's wife)
      - "Greetings: Prints from the Winston Collection,", December 15, 1963-January 31, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "The New Formalists: Paintings for Purchase Consideration,", January 15-February 9, 1964 (Box 5)
        (Milton Cohen and Robert Iglehart, Professors of Art)
      - "History of Art 425-Graphic Art" (Mr. S. Sachs), January-April 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Indian Miniatures" (Archer Collection), February 12-April 6, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Lithographs from the Tamarind Workshop,", March 4-April 12, 1964 (Box 5)
        (University of California, Los Angeles, Art Galleries)
      - "Medieval Exhibition,", April 6-Summer 1964 (Box 5)
        (Mrs. I.H. Forsythe)
      - "Italy Through Dutch Eyes: Dutch Seventeenth Century Landscape Artists in Italy,", April 22-May 24, 1964 (Box 5)
        (Wolfgang Stechow, Visiting Professor of Art)
      - "Contemporary Prints-The Low Countries (Winston Collection),", Spring 1964 (Box 5)
        (J.B. Speed Art Museum)
  - 1964-1965
    - Schedule (Box 5)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1964-1965
      - "Paintings and Drawings by Hale Woodruff,", June 24-July 19, 1964 (Box 5)
        (part of the "Negro Artist in America Today" summer session)
      - "German Expressionist Prints" (Professor Miesel-History of Art 572), June 18-August 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Modern Japanese Calligraphy,", June 21-September 27, 1964 (Box 5)
        (American Federation of Arts; Japan Society, New York and Society for International Cultural Relations, Japan)
      - "Contemporary Sculpture from Museum of Art," July 26-?, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Loans from the Plumer Collection," July-?, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Designed for Production: The Craftsman's Approach,", October 7-31, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "American Drawings,", November 11-December 13, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Cranbrook Loan Exhibition,", January 13-February 7, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "William Blake: Poet, Printer, Prophet,", January 16-February 14, 1965 (Box 5)
        (The Blake Trust)
      - "One Hundred Contemporary American Drawings,", February 24-March 28, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "[Far Eastern Art Study Exhibition] Oriental Section,", March 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Landscapes by Eight Americans,", April 22-May 20, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Architectural and Ornament Drawings of the 16th to the early 19th Centuries in the Collection of the University of Michigan Museum of Art,", May 26-June 27, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1964-1965
      - "Photographs from the Collection of the George Eastman House 1840-1915,", September 1-30, 1964 (Box 5)
        (George Eastman House, Inc.)
      - "The Artist and Popular Movements of the 20th Century,", October 3-26, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "Religious Subjects in Modern Graphic Arts,", October 24-November 15, 1964 (Box 5)
      - "European Prints of the Late Nineteenth Century,", November 20, 1964-January 28, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Memorabilia of the 1913 Armory Show,", February 1-22, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Architecture of Wood,", February 22-March 15, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "The Eskimo in a Changing World,", April 1-25, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Fifty Years of American Prints (from Homer to Hopper),", April 24-May 16, 1965 (Box 5)
  - 1965-1966
    - Schedule (Box 5)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1965-1966
      - "The American Flag,", September 18-October 10, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "Ornamental Decorations,", October 8-29, 1965 (Box 5)
      - "The Artist as Illustrator,", November 5, 1965-January 2, 1966 (Box 5)
      - "Architecture of Industry,", January 3-24, 1966 (Box 5)
      - "The Work of Alvar Aalto,", February 26-March 20, 1966 (Box 5)
      - "Japanese Kabuki Prints,", March 7-11, 1966 (Box 5)
      - "German Medieval Sculpture,", March 30-April 20, 1966 (Box 5)
      - "Twentieth Century American & European Drawings,", December 1966 (Box 5)
        (museum class)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1965-1966
      - "Contemporary Prints from Germany II,", June 29-August 15, 1965 (Box 6)
        (Oregon State University)
      - "23rd National Ceramics Exhibition,", July 5-August 14, 1965 (Box 6)
        (Everson Museum of Art)
      - "Kitchen Gods and Others: Chinese Woodcuts from the Wang Collection,", September 1-30, 1965 (Box 6)
      - "English Mezzotints from the Collection of the Toledo Museum of Art,", October 6-November 7, 1965 (Box 6)
      - "French Watercolors (1750-1850),", September 29-October 24, 1965 (Box 6)
      - "Paintings & Drawings & Sculptures from the Collection of Caroline and Erwin Swann,", November 3-December 5, 1965 (Box 6)
        (Portland Art Museum)
      - "Reflections: the Image of Man,", December 5, 1965-January 16, 1966 (Box 6)
        (graduate seminar in museum philosophy and practice)
      - "[Contemporary] Japanese Abstract Art,", January 19-February 27, 1966 (Box 6)
        (Roland Gibson)
      - "Aesop: Five Centuries of Illustrated Fables,", March 1-22, 1966 (Box 6)
        (includes book)
      - "19th and 20th Century European Drawings,", March 7-27, 1966 (Box 6)
      - "The Architecture of Jacques Brownson,", April 6-May 8, 1966 (Box 6)
      - "Ancient & Islamic Art from Ann Arbor Collections,", April 13-May 8, 1966 (Box 6)
  - 1966-1967
    - Schedule (Box 6)
    - "The Plate, The Block, The Stone, The Print,", February 1-28, 1967 (Box 6)
      (Associated American Artists)
    - "Alessandro Magnasco (1667-1749),", April 23-May 14, 1967 (Box 6)
      (UMMA & J.B. Speed Art Museum)
    - "Rauschenberg: Illustrations for Dante's Inferno,", April 24-May 15, 1967 (Box 6)
  - 1967-1968
    - Schedule (Box 6)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1967-1968
      - "The Painting of Tao-Chi,", August 13-September 17, 1967 (Box 6)
        (see also "Sasanian Silver," August 13-September 17, 1967)
      - "Sasanian Silver: Late Antique and Early Medieval Arts of Luxury from Iran,", August 13-September 17, 1967 (Box 6)
      - "Michigan Alumni Art Collections: Works of Art Selected from the Collections of Alumni of the University of Michigan,", October 1-29, 1967 (Box 6)
      - "Ceramics of Shoji Hamada," [October 1]-24, 1967 (Box 6)
      - "Small Exhibition of Contemporary Sculpture,", October 30, 1967-February 14, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Japanese Prints," December 2, 1967-January 21, 1968[?[ (Box 6)
        (Museum class exhibition)
      - "Contemporary Italian Art from the Roland Gibson Collection,", January 7-February 11, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Selections from the Florence L. Stol Collection,", February 17-April 30, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Alcoa Collection of Contemporary Art,", March 17-April 7, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "15th and 16th Century European Drawings,", May 5-26, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "A University Collects: University of California, Berkeley,", June 9-July 7, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1967-1968
      - "Nineteenth Century French Prints,", October 19, 1967-January 20, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Prints by J.A.M. Whistler,", January 25-March 28, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Contemporary Color Prints,", April 1-June 25, 1968 (Box 6)
  - 1968-1969
    - Schedule (Box 6)
    - Alumni Memorial Hall exhibitions [AMH], 1968-1969
      - "European Drawings from the Sonnenschein Collection,", August 10-October 20, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "Traditional Ibo (Igbo) Sculpture from Biafra,", August 25-September 29, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "A Collection in Progress,", October 4-November 3, 1968 (Box 6)
        (includes label and installation photograph)
      - "Jo Mielziner Designs for the Theatre,", November 15-December 15, 1968 (Box 6)
        (International Exhibitions Foundation)
        (includes label and correspondence with artist)
      - "English Revivalism 1750-1870 The Aesthetic of Nostalgia,", December 8, 1968-January 19, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Art Faculty Annual I,", January 12-February 9, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Manet and Spain,", January 19-March 2, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Josef Albers: White Line Squares" (Los Angeles County Museum of Art), February 9-March 9, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Contemporary Prints from the Collection of Mrs. Lydia Winston Malbin,", February 16-March 16, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "The World of Voltaire,", March 30-May 10, 1969; 2 folders (Box 6)
        (includes curator Paul Grigaut's notes and installation photograph)
      - Renaissance exhibition, April 6-20, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Word and Image: Posters from the Collection of the Museum of Modern Art,", May 21-June 29, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Projected exhibitions (exhibition possibilities), 1969- (Box 6)
    - Undergraduate Library exhibitions [UGLI], 1968-1969
      - "Chagall Color Lithographs: Arabian Nights,", June 25-October 20, 1968 (Box 6)
      - "16th-19th Century Prints and Drawings,", October 27, 1968-February 6, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Photographs by Max Waldman: 'The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat',", February 9-March 23, 1969 (Box 6)
      - "Faces,", April 9-July 14, 1969 (Box 6)
  - 1969-1970
    - Schedule (Box 6)
    - "Graphic Menagerie" [UGLI], July 15-November 11, 1969 (Box 6)
    - "The Square in Painting,", July 6-August 24, 1969 (Box 6)
      (American Federation of Arts
    - "A Connoisseur's Choice: From the Collection of Paul L. Grigaut,", September 14-October 12, 1969 (Box 6)
    - "Expressionism in Europe: 1900-1930,", October 6, 1969-February 23, 1970 (Box 6)
      (includes installation slides)
    - "Contemporary Drawings,", October 19-November 9, 1969 (Box 6)
    - "Selections from the Sixteenth National Print Exhibition: The Brooklyn Museum,", November 16-December 14, 1969 (Box 6)
    - "John Mix Stanley: A Traveler in the West,", December 7, 1969-January 18, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Merrymaking" [UGLI], December 15, 1969-May 2, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Art Faculty Annual II,", January 11-February 8, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Graduate Student Review Exhibition,", January 21-30, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Drawings-French, English and Italian,", February 1970 (Box 6)
      (Professor William Coles, English Department)
    - "Contemporary Ceramics,", February 3-March 8, 1970 (Box 6)
      (in cooperation with the Art Department)
    - "The Joseph H. Hazen Collection,", February 15-March 15, 1970 (Box 6)
      (Art Gallery, University of Notre Dame?)
    - "American Representational Art of the 1920s and 1930s,", March 1-April 12, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Acquisitions for Permanent Collection 1969-1970,", April-May 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Women at Michigan 1870-1970,", April 26-May 24, 1970 (Box 6)
      (Michigan Historical Collections)
      (in connection with centennial of admission of women to the University of Michigan)
    - "Collector's Exhibition: Marvin Felheim,", April 19-July 19, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Two Centuries of French Illustrators" [UGLI], May 6-October 16, 1970 (Box 6)
  - 1970-1971
    - Schedule (Box 6)
    - "Painterly Realism,", July 5-August 16, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Sculpture and Sculptors' Drawings and Prints (Museum Collections," July-, September 16, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "The Cult of Krishna,", August 2-September 27, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "Prints: 16th and 17th Centuries" (UMMA, Detroit Institute of Arts and Cooper-Hewitt Museum collections), September 6-October 25, 1970 (Box 6)
    - "In Pursuit of Antiquity: Chinese Paintings of the Ming and Ch'ing Dynasties from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. Earl Morse,", September 13-October 25, 1970 (Box 7)
    - "African and Oceanic Art: The La More Collection,", October 2-December 16, 1970 (Box 7)
    - "The World of Margaret Bourke-White,", October 7-November 15, 1970 (Box 7)
    - "American Landscape Architecture (Professional Awards Exhibition)" [UGLI], October 21-November 9, 1970 (Box 7)
      (American Society of Landscape Architects)
    - "Contemporary American Sculpture Selection 2,", November 1-December 6, 1970 (Box 7)
      (Whitney Museum of Art)
    - "Chinoiserie: Fantasy in the Age of Reason,", December 6, 1970-January 17, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "The American Scene Between the Wars" [UGLI], December 21, 1970-February 3, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Art Faculty Annual II,", January 13-February 14, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Graduate Review Show,", January 24-February 21, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Mexican Graphics" [UGLI], February 3-April 25, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Contemporary Prints from the Museum's Collections,", February 28-March 28, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Architectural and Ornamental Drawings: 16th-18th Centuries from the Collections of the UMMA,", February 28-May 31, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Collector's Choice: Contemporary Prints from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. C.D. Clark,", April 1-June 27, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Jules Olitski: Contemporary Arts Project,", April 11-May 9, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "25th Annual Water Color Society Exhibition,", May 16-June 13, 1971 (Box 7)
      (Michigan Water Color Society)
  - 1971-1972
    - Schedule (Box 7)
    - "English Prints: 18th and 19th Century" [UGLI], May 3-November 2, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "19th and 20th Century Graphic Art,", June 14-October 13, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Antoni Tapies Print Exhibition,", June 20-August 8, 1971 (Box 7)
      (Martha Jackson Gallery)
    - "Mexican Colonial Painting: The Fenton R. McCreery Collection,", June 27-August 22, 1971 (Box 7)
      (Flint Institute of Arts)
    - "Durer's Cities: Nuremberg and Venice,", September 19-October 17, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Walker Evans Photography,", October 27-December 5, 1971; 2 folders (Box 7)
      (includes artist's lecture on 2 reel-to-reel tapes and 1 audiocassette)
    - "Photographs for Purchase Consideration,", October 27-December 5, 1971 (Box 7)
    - "Two Expressionists: Beckmann and Rouault" [UGLI], November 4, 1971-May 10, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Rome Through the Eyes of the 18th Century,", December 5, 1971-January 16, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Nineteenth and Twentieth Century Graphics,", December 13, 1971-February 13, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Art Faculty Annual IV,", January 16-February 16, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Mid-Year Directions (Graduate Student Show),", February 2-28, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "African and Oceanic Art,", February 27-April 5, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Collectors' Choice[: Professors Ernst Pulgram and William Muschenheim],", March 5-August 7, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Art and the Excited Spirit: America in the Romantic Period,", March 19-May 14, 1972; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - "Nakabayashi Chikuto,", April 18-October 20, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "The World Between the Ox and the Swine: Dada Drawings by Hans Richter," May 3-June 11, 192 (Box 7)
      (Museum of Art, Rhode Island School of Design)
    - "Contemporary Prints" [UGLI], May 10-?, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Posters and Portfolios from the Collection of Lydia and Harry Winston (Dr. and Mrs. Barnett Malbin, Birmingham, MI),", May 21-June 18, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Indian Miniatures: The Watson Collection, University of Wisconsin,", June 25-August 20, 1972 (Box 7)
      (Elvehjem Art Center, The University of Wisconsin)
  - 1972-1973
    - Schedule (Box 7)
    - "Graphics 72-Japan,", July 9-August 13, 1972 (Box 7)
      (University of Kentucky Art Gallery)
    - "Josef Albers 'Formulation: Articulation',", August 21-November 6, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Daumier and His Contemporaries" [UGLI], August-, September 26, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "The Etching (UMMA Collections),", August 11-November 26, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Contemporary Art: The Collection of Dr. and Mrs. Joseph A. Gosman,", September 13-October 15, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "The Ann Arbor Art Association Collection" (Gift to the UMMA), September 21-October 29, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "The Museum Collects: Objects for Purchase Consideration,", October 22-November 19, 1972 (Box 7)
    - "Andy Warhol,", November 5-December 3, 1972 (Box 7)
      (Graphic Arts course, History of Art 525)
      (includes poster)
    - "The Visionary Experience,", November 12, 1972-January 14, 1973 (Box 7)
      (1972 Graphic Arts course, History of Art 525)
    - "Japanese Mini-Show II" (Maruyama, Shijo and Kishi School Painting), November 21, 1972-January 7, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Photography" [UGLI], November 30, 1972-April 2, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Art Faculty Annual V,", January 21-February 25, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Mid-Year Directions (MFA Graduate Student Exhibition),", January 28-March 4, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "The Form of Cities in Perspective 500 B.C.-A.D. 2000 An Exhibition of Drawings by Charles A. Blessing,", February 28-March 25, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Arts of New Guinea: Selections from the Papo Collection,", March 28-May 6, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Mexican Prints" [UGLI], April 3-July 11, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Collector's Choice,", April 11-October 5, 1973 (Box 7)
      (anonymous lender)
    - Prints and Drawings on Exhibition for Professor Graham Smith's Course, April 1973 (Box 7)
    - "American Posters of the Great War,", April 15-September 10, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Graphic Art of German Expressionism,", May 13-June 17, 1973 (Box 7)
      (Institute of Foreign Relations, Stuttgart, Germany)
  - 1973-1974
    - Schedule (Box 7)
    - "Bauhaus: Lutzeier Collection,", September 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Walter Gropius- 1883-1969 A Photographic Retrospective," September 1-30, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "New Art Faculty,", September 18-November 1, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "19th Century Songsheets" (American Illustrated Sheet Music), October 11-November 18, 1973 (Box 7)
      (UMMA and Clements Library)
    - "Hans Hoffman: 52 Works on Paper,", October 15-November 15, 1973 (Box 7)
    - "German Expressionist Paintings, Drawings & Prints" (UMMA Collections), November 20-[December], 1973 (Box 7)
    - "Bauhaus,", December 9, 1973-January 27, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "The Poet-Painters: Buson and His Followers,", January 9-February 17, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "Paintings from Midwestern University Collections: 17th-20th Centuries" (Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) Exhibition), March 17-April 12, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "A Director's Choice: 1946-1956 Jean Paul Slusser,", May 4-27, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "Woodner Collection II: Old Master Drawings,", June 2-July 7, 1974 (Box 7)
      (William H. Schab Gallery)
    - "Lesser Known Prints from the Museum of Art Collection" [UGLI], June-November 1974 (Box 7)
  - 1974-1975
    - Schedule (Box 7)
    - "Discoveries in Watercolor: Paul Jenkins,", July 14-August 11, 1974 (Box 7)
      (Corcoran Gallery of Art)
      (includes brochure)
    - "Ann Arbor Architecture, 1800-1918,", August 25-September 22, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "Architecture and Design: Reginald Malcolmson (Visionary Projects for Buildings and Cities),", September 1-30, 1974 (Box 7)
    - "Drawings by 17th Century Italian Masters from the Collection of Janos Scholz,", October 1974 (Box 7)
      (The Art Galleries, University of California, Santa Barbara(The Art Galleries, University of California, Santa Barbara)
    - "Color in Art,", November 1-30, 1974 (Box 7)
      (Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University)
      (includes photocopies of labels)
    - "Felix Bracquemond and the Etching Process (An Exhibition of Prints & Drawings from the John Taylor Arms Collection, The College of Wooster),", November 1-30, 1974 (Box 7)
      (John Carroll University Fine Arts Gallery and The College of Wooster Art Center Museum)
      (includes announcement)
    - "Drawings from the Sonnenschein Collection,", December 15, 1974-January 12, 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Indian Miniatures from the Collection of Edwin Binney 3rd,", January 26-February 23, 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Calligraphy Mini-Show,", January 15-April 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Reflections of an Era of Change: The Art of France 1774-1830,", March 12-April 6, 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Art Faculty '75: An Exhibition of Works by the Art Faculty of the University of Michigan,", April 16-July 6, 1975 (Box 7)
  - 1975-1976
    - Schedule (Box 7)
    - "Käthe Kollwitz: A Selection of Prints from the Landauer Collection,", July 18-September 21, 1975 (Box 7)
      (William Benton Museum of Art, University of Connecticut)
    - "The Sculpture of Richard Hunt,", September 10-October 23, 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Eighteenth Century French Prints and Drawings,", October 5-November 9, 1975 (Box 7)
    - "Images of Love and Death in Late Medieval and Renaissance Art,", November 21, 1975-January 4, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Joan Miró: The Mallorca Suite,", January 15-February 15, 1976 (Box 8)
      (includes pamphlet)
    - "The Art of Wen Chen-ming (1470-1559),", January 25-February 29, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Surrealist exhibition [UGLI], Winter 1975 (Box 8)
    - "One Eye View: The Impact of Photography on Paintings and Prints Since 1960,", February 25-March 27, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "Karl Struss: Man with a Camera,", February 25-March 28, 1976 (Box 8)
      (Cranbrook Academy of Art/Museum)
    - Study exhibition-Graham Smith's History of Art course, February 23-March 31, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "A Flower for Every Season: Japanese Paintings from the C.D. Carter Collection,", March 21-April 25, 1976 (Box 8)
      (The Brooklyn Museum)
    - "Robert Motherwell: Selected Prints 1961-1974,", April 5-May 16, 1976 (Box 8)
      (E.D.O. Comprehensive Exhibition Services)
    - "Edvard Munch: The Major Graphics,", May 29-August 15, 1976 (Box 8)
  - 1976-1977
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "Contemporary Reflections 1971-1974,", August 29-September 26, 1976 (Box 8)
      (Alrich Museum of Contemporary Art, American Federation of Arts)
    - "Art Between the Wars,", October 4-31, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "American Abstraction-Creation 1932-36: Paintings and Studies by Alexander Corazzo and LeRoy Turner,", October 4-31, 1976 (Box 8)
    - "The Borden Limner and His Contemporaries," November 14, 1976-January 16, 197 (Box 8)
      (Robert C.H. Bishop, Greenfield Village and Henry Ford Museum)
    - "Indian Art from the George P. Bickford Collection,", January 2-February 13, 1977 (Box 8)
      (Cleveland Museum of Art)
    - "Conversion of the Magdalene (Caravaggio),", February 16-March 15, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Art School Faculty,", February 25-March 23, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Pompeii as Source and Inspiration: Reflections in Eighteenth-and Nineteenth-Century Art" (Box 8)
  - 1977-1978
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "The Etching,", June 12-August 14, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Photographs: 19th and 20th Century,", June 12-August 14, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Recent Acquisitions on Paper,", June 19-August 14, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Alfred Stevens,", August 28-October 16, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Through Closed Doors: Western Influence on Japanese Art (1650-1830),", October 9-November 3, 1977 (Box 8)
    - "Works from the Collection of Dorothy and Herbert Vogel,", November 11, 1977-January 1, 1978 (Box 8)
      (includes correspondence with Mrs. Vogel)
    - Peter Campus exhibition, January 8-28, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Nineteenth Century Lithographs; Marc Chagall; Max Pechstein The Lord's Prayer, mid-February-mid-March, 1978 (Box 8)
    - "J.B. Yeats Broadsides," ca., March 1978 (Box 8)
    - "Chicago: The City and Its Artists, 1945-1978,", March 17-April 23, 1978 (Box 8)
    - "From Delacroix to Cezanne: French Watercolor Landscapes of the Nineteenth Century,", April 1-May 14, 1979 (Box 8)
      (Art Gallery, University of Maryland)
  - 1978-1979
    - Schedule (Box 8)
    - "Project New Urban Monuments,", May 12-September 10, 1978 (Box 8)
      (Akron Art Institute)
    - "Atelier 17,", June 4-July 30, 1978 (Box 8)
      (Elvehjem Art Center, University of Wisconsin-Madison)
    - "Whistler: The Later Years [1879-1903],", August 27-October 8, 1978 (Box 8)